Finding Aid for Norris Family Papers 1815-1960
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Norris Family Papers 1815-1960
Norris family.
1 oversize folder
3 linear feet
Norris family of Ypsilanti and Grand Rapids, Michigan. Papers of Mark Norris, Ypsilanti businessman and postmaster; papers of his wife, Roccena Vaill Norris, local teacher and woman's rights advocate; papers of their son, Lyman, attorney and regent of the University of Michigan, 1883-1884; papers of Lyman's son, Mark Norris, Grand Rapids attorney and Grand Master of the Knights Templar in the United States; papers of Lyman's daughter Maria Norris, Grand Rapids physician; papers of Mark's son, Abbott Norris; and related papers of other family members, notably the Whittelsey family of Connecticut.
85830 Aa 2 Ac
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection was donated by Margaret Abbott Norris (donor no. 3927) in 1962. Additional materials were transferred from the Graduate Library of the University of Michigan (donor no. 1278 )
The collection is open for research.
The papers of the Norris family cover four generations, 1815-1960, in the lives of an Ypsilanti and Grand Rapids family. The first member of the family represented in the papers is Mark Norris (1796-1862). Mark Norris was born in Vermont, but by 1820 he was a businessman and postmaster in Covington, New York where he married Roccena B. Vaill (1797-1876). She was the daughter of James and Helen Compton Vaill and taught school in Covington. Mark and Roccena had two children, Elvira (b. 1821), who married Benjamin Follett in 1841; and Lyman Decatur (1823-1894).
Around 1828, largely because of anti-Masonic sentiment, the Norrises moved to the Ypsilanti, Michigan area. Roccena taught school briefly and Mark worked as postmaster while conducting other business interests. When his health failed in the late 1850's, the Norrises' son, Lyman Decatur, took over the family's business affairs.
Lyman D. Norris studied at Marshall College from 1839-1841. He then became the first student to matriculate at the University of Michigan in the fall of 1841. He studied further at Yale from 1844-1845 and graduated in 1845 with degrees from both universities.
Norris read law in Detroit with Alexander Fraser, was admitted to the bar in 1847, and began his practice in St. Louis, Missouri the following year. During the early 1850's he studied and traveled in Europe. In 1852, Norris participated on the state level in the Dred Scott slavery case as counsel for Scott's owner, Dr. John Emerson. Throughout his career in St. Louis, Norris was involved in local Democratic politics. Lyman D. Norris practiced law in Ypsilanti from 1854-1871 and then in Grand Rapids from 1871 until his death in 1894. In his later years he was fairly active in state Democratic politics and University of Michigan affairs, being appointed a regent in 1883.
Lyman D. Norris married Lucy Alsop Whittelsey of Middletown, Connecticut in 1854. They had two living children: Mark Norris (1857-1943) and Maria W. Norris (ca. 1858-1938). The son, Mark Norris studied at the University of Michigan and graduated from the law school in 1882. He practiced law with his father, Lyman D. Norris, for several years in Grand Rapids, and was very active in the Masonic Order being elected Grand Master in 1937. His son, Abbott L. Norris carried on the family law offices. Maria W. Norris was educated in Montreal and Boston. She studied medicine and later became a prominent Grand Rapids physician.
The Norris family papers consists of three linear feet of correspondence, business papers, and scrapbooks. The bulk of the papers are letters among various family members which contain a wealth of information about 19th century daily life, social conditions, business affairs, and local and state politics. This collection is especially useful in researching: women's history; Norris family and kinship interrelationships; early area settlement and local history; university student life at the University of Michigan and elsewhere; 19th century economic conditions and political issues; and 20th century Freemasonry.
Subjects:
Adams, Charles Kendall, 1835-1902.; Antislavery movements--United States.; Banks and banking--Michigan.; Education--United States.; Elections--Michigan--1875.; Europe--Description and travel.; First Presbyterian Church (Ypsilanti, Mich.); Freemasonry--Michigan.; Grand Rapids (Mich.); Knights Templar (Masonic order); Marshall College (Marshall, Mich.); Michigan--Politics and government--1837-1950.; Michigan--Politics and government--1866-1876.; Michigan--Politics and government--1877-1898.; Michigan--Politics and government--1939-1945.; Norris family.; Physicians--Michigan--Grand Rapids.; Presbyterian Church--Michigan--Ypsilanti.; Railroads--Michigan.; Scott, Dred, 1809-1858.; Social reformers--Michigan--Ypsilanti.; Teachers--Michigan--Ypsilanti.; Travelers.; United States--History--Civil War, 1861-1865.; United States--Politics and government--1865-1877.; University of Michigan. Board of Regents.; University of Michigan. School of Dentistry.; University of Michigan--Students--Social life and customs--1841-1850.; University of Michigan--Students--Social life and customs--1871-1880.; University of Michigan--Student notebooks.; Voyages and travels.; Women physicians--Michigan--Grand Rapids.; Women social reformers--Michigan--Ypsilanti.; Women teachers--Michigan--Ypsilanti.; Women's rights--Michigan.; Women--Suffrage--Michigan.; Yale University.; Ypsilanti (Mich.)
Subjects - Visual Material:
Alpha Delta Phi. Peninsular Chapter (University of Michigan); Norris, Lyman, 1823-1894.; Norris, Mark, 1857-1943.; University of Michigan--Students--1871-1880.
Contributors:
Abbott, James.; Allen, John, 1796-1851.; Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.; Biddle, John, 1792-1859.; Brown, Prentiss Marsh, 1889-1973.; Burgoyne, John.; Cass, Lewis, 1782-1866.; Clark, Mary H., d. 1875.; Conant, Shubael, b. 1783.; Crary, Isaac Edwin, 1804-1854.; Dickinson, Donald McDonald, 1846-1917.; Ferguson, Homer, 1889-1982.; Ferris, Woodbridge N., 1853-1928.; Gray, Fanny, d.1911.; Gray, Mary Bury, 1820-1909.; Horsford, M. C. Mrs., d.1859.; Jones, J. Elizabeth (Jane Elizabeth), 1813-1896.; Jonkman, Bartel J. (Bartel John), 1884-1955.; Kirkland, Caroline M. (Caroline Matilda), 1801-1864.; Knapp, Andrew B.; Knapp, George.; Lyon, Lucius, 1800-1851.; Mapes, Carl Edgar, 1874-1939.; Norris, Abbott.; Norris, Lyman, 1823-1894.; Norris, Maria, 1856-1938.; Norris, Mark, 1796-1862.; Norris, Mark, 1857-1943.; Norris, Roccena Vaill, 1797-1876.; Norvell, John, 1789-1850.; Palmer, Thomas Witherell, 1830-1913.; Rogers, Abigail C., 1818-1869.; Sheldon, E. M. (Electa Maria), 1817-1902.; Taft, J. (Jonathan), 1820-1903.; Trowbridge, C. C. (Charles Christopher), 1800-1883.; Victor, Frances Fuller, 1826-1902.; Victor, Metta Victoria Fuller, 1831-1885.; Weed, Caroline.; Wheeler, Burton K. (Burton Kendall), 1882-1975.; Whittelsey family.; Woodbridge, William, 1780-1861.; Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.
Genre/Form:
Photographs.; Prints.; Scrapbooks.
- Mark Norris (1796-1862)
  The papers of Mark Norris cover the period 1825-1859 and consist of business papers and correspondence regarding banking, milling and railroads, and some letters with his wife Roccena, brother-in-law Benjamin Vaill and son-in-law Benjamin Follett. Included are a long series of letters from the Norrises' son, Lyman Decatur, concerning his student days at Marshall, the University of Michigan and Yale, 1831-1845; his subsequent travels through Europe, 1850-1851; and his legal career, including a letter, March 31, 1852, about the Dred Scott case.
  - Papers (including business correspondence and related materials)
    - 1825-1827 (Box 1)
      (1-1)
    - 1828-1829 (Box 1)
      (1-2)
    - 1830 (Box 1)
      (1-3)
    - 1831 (Box 1)
      (1-4)
    - 1832 (Box 1)
      (1-5)
    - 1833-1834 (Box 1)
      (1-6)
    - 1835 (Box 1)
      (1-7)
    - 1836 (Box 1)
      (1-8)
    - 1837 (Box 1)
      (1-9)
    - 1838 (Box 1)
      (1-10)
    - 1839 (Box 1)
      (1-11)
    - 1840 (Box 1)
      (1-12)
    - 1841 (Box 1)
      (1-13)
    - 1842-1843 (Box 1)
      (1-14)
    - 1856 (Box 1)
      (1-15)
    - 1857-1862 (Box 1)
      (1-16)
  - Papers circa 1831-1854 (Box 1)
    include warranty deeds and land agreements for Norris properties
    (1-17)
  - Letters (to and from wife Roccena B. Vaill Norris)
    - 1838, 1840, 1850-1854 (Box 1)
      (1-18)
    - 1856, 1858 (Box 1)
      (1-19)
    - Letters (to and from son Lyman Decatur Norris addressed to both parents) (Box 1)
    - 1832, 1839 (Box 1)
      (1-20)
    - 1840 (Box 1)
      (1-21)
    - 1841, 1843 (Box 1)
      (1-22)
    - 1844 (Box 1)
      (1-23)
    - 1845 (Box 1)
      (1-24)
    - 1847-1848 (Box 1)
      (1-25)
    - 1849 (Box 1)
      (1-26)
    - 1850 (Box 1)
      (1-27)
    - 1851 (Box 1)
      (1-28)
    - 1852 (Box 1)
      (1-29)
    - 1853-1855 (Box 1)
      (1-30)
    - 1856-1859 (Box 1)
      (1-31)
- Roccena B. (Vaill) Norris (1797-1876), wife of Mark Norris
  The papers of Roccena B. Vaill Norris cover 1825-1876 and consist mainly of letters with friends and early feminist leaders. There is also correspondence with daughter Elvira Norris Follett and son Lyman Decatur, and letters with other relatives including her sister Lucinda, brother-in-law George Knapp and Civil War letters from nephew Andrew Knapp.
  Throughout her life Roccena Norris was active in a variety of literary and charitable pursuits. She was also greatly interested in women's rights, especially with higher education for women and the suffrage movement. In this regard, she corresponded frequently with early feminists Caroline Kirkland and Electa M. Sheldon (later Electa Stewart), among others. Roccena Norris also did mission work through the Presbyterian Church and the local Ladies Home Association of which she was president for over sixteen years. In addition, she helped found the Ladies Library Association in 1868 and was one of its strongest supporters.
  - Letters with friends and relatives
    - circa 1825-1840 (Box 1)
      (1-32)
    - 1845-1851 (Box 1)
      (1-33)
    - 1852-1853 (Box 1)
      (1-34)
    - 1854-1855 (Box 1)
      (1-35)
    - 1856-1857 (Box 1)
      (1-36)
    - 1858 (Box 1)
      (1-37)
    - 1859-1860 (Box 1)
      (1-38)
    - 1861-1862 (Box 1)
      (1-39)
    - 1863-1864 (Box 1)
      (1-40)
    - 1865-1868 (Box 1)
      (1-41)
    - 1869-1870 (Box 1)
      (1-42)
    - 1871-1872 (Box 1)
      (1-43)
    - 1873-1875 (Box 1)
      (1-44)
  - Letters with daughter, Elvira Norris Follett 1836-1842 (Box 1)
    (1-45)
  - Letters with son, Lyman Decatur Norris
    - 1862-1865 (Box 1)
      (1-46)
    - 1866-1871 (Box 1)
      (1-47)
    - 1872-1874 (Box 1)
      (1-48)
    - 1875 (Box 1)
      (1-49)
    - 1876 (Box 1)
      (1-50)
- Lyman Decatur Norris (1823-1894), son of Mark and Roccena, Norris
  The papers of Lyman Decatur Norris span the years 1837-1891 and consist of some business and legal correspondence regarding 1870's politics and University of Michigan regental matters. Among his personal correspondence are letters with his wife, Lucy Whittelsey Norris, mainly concerning family matters and daily life; letters from their children, Mark and Maria; and correspondence with other friends and relatives, including sister, Elvira N. Follett.
  - Papers (including business and political correspondence and related financial materials)
    - 1845, 1852-1862 (Box 2)
      (2-1)
    - 1863-1866 (Box 2)
      (2-2)
    - 1867-1871, 1873 (Box 2)
      (2-3)
    - 1874-1875 (Box 2)
      (2-4)
    - 1876-1877 (Box 2)
      (2-5)
    - 1883, 1885, 1889, 1891 (Box 2)
      (2-6)
  - Speeches and briefs
    - circa 1866 1880 (Box 2)
      (2-7)
  - Letters with sister and brother-in-law, Elvira N. and Ben Follett
    - circa 1839-1852 (scattered dates) (Box 2)
      (2-8)
  - Letters with wife, Lucy A. (Whittelsey) Norris
    - 1862 (Box 2)
      (2-9)
    - 1864 (Box 2)
      (2-10)
    - 1865 (Box 2)
      (2-11)
    - 1866 (Box 2)
      (2-12)
    - 1867 (Box 2)
      (2-13)
    - 1868 (Box 2)
      (2-14)
    - 1869 (Box 2)
      (2-15)
    - 1874-1875 (Box 2)
      (2-16)
    - 1876-1878 (Box 2)
      (2-17)
    - 1883-1891 (scattered dates) (Box 2)
      (2-18)
  - Letters with children, Mark and Maria
    - 1872-1875 (Box 2)
      (2-19)
    - 1889-1890 (Box 2)
      (2-20)
  - Letters with friends and relatives
    - circa 1837-1875 (scattered dates) (Box 2)
      (2-21)
  - Mortgage bond (Folder 1)
    (located in Ac)
  - Miscellaneous papers, fragments, and newspaper clippings (Box 2)
    (2-22)
  - Scrapbook concerning Civil War and post-war politics circa 1861-1886 (Box 2)
    (2-23)
- Lucy A. (Whittelsey) Norris, wife of Lyman D. Norris
  The papers of Lucy Whittelsey Norris cover 1862-1891 and consist of correspondence with her relatives and friends, including a separate series with her mother, Sarah Tracy Whittelsey 1869-1877; and with her children.
  (See also related Whittelsey material listed below)
  - Letters with friends and relatives
    - 1862-1865 (Box 2)
      (2-24)
    - 1867 (Box 2)
      (2-25)
    - 1868-1869 (Box 2)
      (2-26)
    - 1873 (Box 2)
      (2-27)
    - 1874-1875 (Box 2)
      (2-28)
  - Letters with mother, Sarah Whittelsey
    - 1876-1877, 1891 (Box 2)
      (2-29)
    - 1869, 1872 (Box 2)
      (2-30)
    - January-May 1873 (Box 2)
      (2-31)
    - June-December 1873 (Box 2)
      (2-32)
    - 1874, 1875 (Box 2)
      (2-33)
    - 1876 (Box 2)
      (2-34)
    - 1877 (Box 2)
      (2-35)
  - Letters with children, Mark and Maria
    - 1872, 1873 (Box 2)
      (2-36)
    - 1875 (Box 2)
      (2-37)
    - 1875-1877, 1880, 1891 (Box 2)
      (2-38)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and financial papers (undated and fragmentary) (Box 2)
    (2-39)
- Norris family material
  Miscellaneous Norris family material, including notes, invitations and circulars.
  - Miscellaneous letters (Box 2)
    (2-40)
  - Miscellaneous notes and invitations (Box 2)
    (2-41)
  - Miscellaneous business notes and circulars (Box 2)
    (2-42)
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box 2)
    (2-43)
- Whittelsey family (letters of parents and other relatives of Lucy A. Whittelsey Norris)
  Additional Whittelsey family material, consisting of some letters of Lucy's parents, Chauncey and Sarah Whittelsey, and her brothers, Charles Chauncey of St. Louis and Eben, who died in the Civil War, August, 1862.
  - Chauncey Whittelsey, father of Lucy Whittelsey Norris
    - Letters (primarily business)
      - 1816, 1822-1824 (Box 2)
        (2-44)
      - 1825-1826 (Box 2)
        (2-45)
      - 1827 (Box 2)
        (2-46)
      - 1828-1829 (Box 2)
        (2-47)
      - 1830-1831, 1836 (Box 2)
        (2-48)
  - Sarah T. Whittelsey, mother of Lucy Whittelsey Norris
    - Letters with husband, Chauncey Whittelsey
      - 1824 (Box 2)
        (2-49)
      - 1825-1826 (Box 2)
        (2-50)
      - 1827 (Box 2)
        (2-51)
    - Letters with son, Charles Chauncey Whittelsey
      - 1850, 1852-1854, 1870-1871 (Box 2)
        (2-52)
    - Letters with friends and relatives circa 1840-1888 (scattered dates) (Box 2)
      (2-53)
  - Eben F. Whittelsey (d. 1862), brother of Lucy Whittelsey Norris
    - Letters (primarily business)
      - 1857-1858 (Box 2)
        (2-54)
      - 1859 (Box 2)
        (2-55)
      - 1860 (Box 2)
        (2-56)
    - Miscellaneous letters circa 1819-1853 (fragmentary and unidentified) (Box 2)
      (2-57)
- Mark Norris (1857-1943)
  The papers of Mark Norris, son of Lyman D. and Lucy Norris, cover the years 1883-1942 and deal mostly with Freemasonry activities and his election as Grand Master in 1937.
  - Legal papers and miscellaneous correspondence circa 1883-1937 (scattered dates) (Box 3)
    (3-1)
  - Speeches, drafts and related materials (primarily of Freemasons)
    - Undated (Box 3)
      (3-2; 3-3)
    - circa 1918-1934 (scattered dates) (Box 3)
      (3-4)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 3)
      (3-5)
    - 1938 (Box 3)
      (3-6)
    - 1939 (Box 3)
      (3-7)
    - 1940 (Box 3)
      (3-8)
  - Masonic programs and related correspondence
    - July 1-July 20, 1937 (Box 3)
      (3-9)
    - July 21-July 31, 1937 (Box 3)
      (3-10)
    - August-December 1937, 1940 (Box 3)
      (3-11)
  - Miscellaneous Freemason publications and related materials
    - circa 1918-1935 (scattered dates) (Box 3)
      (3-12)
    - circa 1936-1940 (scattered dates) (Box 3)
      (3-13)
  - Miscellaneous papers and clippings undated (Box 3)
    (3-14)
  - Biographical material-by and about Mark Norris (Box 3)
    (3-15)
  - Biographical material-obituary (Box 3)
    (3-16)
  - Citations received, 5 items (Folder 1)
  - Bound material
    - College scrapbook, 1875-1878 (Box 3)
      (3-17)
    - College notebook 1877 (Box 3)
      (3-18)
    - Masonic record book 1899-1937 (Box 3)
      (3-19)
    - Cash book record May 1934-November 1942 (Box 3)
      (3-20)
- Abbott Norris
  The papers of Abbott Norris, son of Mark and Cornella Norris, cover the years 1936-1960 and consist of correspondence with members of Congress including Bartel Jonkman, Carl Mapes, Arthur Vandenberg and Burton Wheeler, among others, concerning taxes and pending legislation.
  - Correspondence with Congressional members
    - 1936-1938 (Box 3)
      (3-21)
    - 1939-1941 (Box 3)
      (3-22)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 3)
      (3-23)
    - 1944-1946 (Box 3)
      (3-24)
  - Miscellaneous papers
    - circa 1946-1960 (scattered dates) (Box 3)
      (3-25)
- Photographs
  - Portraits of Lyman and Mark Norris, and group portrait of Alpha Delta Phi fraternity at the University of Michigan circa 1879 (Box 3)
Selective Index to Norris family correspondence
Mark Norris Correspondence
Abbott, James
Feb. 23, 1830
Allen, John, 1796-1851.
Aug. 19, 1834
Biddle, John, 1789-1859.
Nov. 4, 1834; Jan. 8, 1836; and Apr. 6, 1836
Cass, Lewis, 1782-1866.
Mar. 31, 1852; and Apr. 30, 1852
Conant, Shubael
Apr. 29, 1841; May 20, 1841; and Dec. 3, 1841
Crary, Isaac Edwin, 1804-1854.
Mar. 31, 1852; and Dec. 16, 1835
Knapp, George
Feb. 2, 1831; Aug. 8, 1831; Aug. 22, 1831; Sept. 1, 1831; Sept. 29, 1831; Oct. 19, 1832; Jan. 27, 1837; and Dec. 22, 1841
Lyon Lucius, 1800-1851.
Dec. 22, 1833; July 23, 1835; Sept. 30, 1835; Jan. 8, 1836; Feb. 7, 1836; Feb. 23, 1836; Aug. 23, 1836; Sept. 8, 1836; Oct. 14, 1836; Oct. 27, 1836; Jan. 30, 1837; Feb. 27, 1837; Feb. 28, 1837; Mar. 28, 1837; June 16, 1837; Nov. 29, 1837; Dec. 11, 1837; Dec. 22, 1837; Dec. 25, 1837; Jan. 5, 1838; Jan. 11, 1838; Feb. 10, 1838; Mar. 2, 1838; Mar. 26, 1838; Apr. 4, 1838; Apr. 27, 1838; Feb. 4, 1839; and Feb. 18, 1839
Norvell, John, 1789-1850.
July 15, 1834; Aug. 27, 1834; and Oct. 10, 1834
Trowbridge, C. C. (Charles Christopher), 1800-1883.
Jan. 30, 1836; Mar. 24, 1840; and June 11, 1840
Roccena Norris Correspondence
Burgoyne, John
[in folder 1-40] March 1, 1863; April 3, 1863; June 26, 1863; July 12, 1864; August 24, 1864
Clark, Mary H., d. 1875.
Nov. 20, 1851; and Apr. 3, 1852
Gray, Fanny, d. 1911.
July 22, 1862; Nov. 3, 1862; Nov. 25, 1862; Jan. 31, 1870; May 9, 1870; Aug. 18, 1870; Oct. 14, 1870; Jan. 10, 1872; July 28, 1872; Nov. 14, 1872; Mar. 15, 1874
Gray, Mary Bury, 1820-1909.
Apr. 3, 1862; June 16, 1862; June 30, 1862; July 14, 1862; and Aug. 1, 1862
Horsford, M. C., Mrs., d.1859.
Mar. 6, 1857; Mar. 11, 1857; May 11, 1857; June 28, 1857; Aug. 11, 1857; Oct. 9, 1857; Nov. 17, 1857; undated ca. 1858; Feb. 24, 1858; Apr. 20, 1858; May 2, 1858; July 17, 1858; Oct. 1, 1858; Dec. 9, 1858; Apr. 3, 1859; Apr. 5, 1859; June 30, 1859
Knapp, Andrew B.
Dec. 12, 1856; July 30, 1860; Aug. 10, 1860; Aug. 26, 1860; Sept. 23, 1860; Oct. 24, 1860; Dec. 23, 1860; May 8, 1862; July 7, 1862; Sept. 2, 1862; Mar. 14, 1863; May 28, 1863; Jan. 23, 1866; Mar. 4, 1866; Mar. 24, 1866; May 4, 1866; May 9, 1873
Knapp, George
Sept. 30, 1830; Apr. 15, 1831; July 25, 1854; Apr. 8, 1861; Apr. 14, 1866
Jones, J. Elizabeth (Jane Elizabeth), 1813-1896.
Feb. 14, 1851; Feb. 21, 1851; Mar. 24, 1851; Aug. 5, 1851; Sept. 7, 1851
Kirkland, Caroline M. (Caroline Matilda), 1801-1864.
Jan. 8, 1848; Nov. 11, 1848; Aug. 3, 1851; Apr. 6, 1862
Rogers, Abigail C., 1818-1869.
Jan. 13, 1864; May 31, 1867; June 21, 1869; June 17, 1869; Aug. 9, 1869
Sheldon, E M. (Electa Maria), 1817-1902.
Dec. 5, 1851; June 28, 1852; July 12, 1852; July 21, 1852; Nov. 3, 1852; Nov. 11, 1852; Feb. 16, 1853; Feb. 17, 1853; Oct. 13, 1853; Jan. 14, 1854; Feb. 2, 1854; Feb. 18, 1854; May 30, 1854; June 27, 1854; July 27, 1854; Aug. 16, 1854; Aug. 21, 1854; Aug. 22, 1854; Sept. 13, 1854; Nov. 14, 1854; Feb. 23, 1855; Mar. 8, 1855; Apr. 7, 1855; Apr. 23, 1855; July 6, 1855; Sept. 8, 1855; Oct. 23, 1855; Jan. 27, 1856; Jan. 24, 1857; Feb. 27, 1857; May 28, 1857; Dec. 16, 1857 (with F. Fuller); June 29, 1858; Feb. 3, 1859; May 3, 1859; May 9, 1859; June 18, 1859; June 20, 1859; July 1, 1859; July 22, 1859; Aug. 23, 1860; Jan. 25, 1862; July 6, 1863; Aug. 8, 1863; Apr. 26, 1864; Sept 26, 1864; (Stewart) Mar. 6, 1865; Dec. 26, 1868; June 7, 1869; Oct. 26, 1899; June 16, 1870; July 28, 1871; Feb. 29, 1875; Mar. 29, 1875; July 26, 1875; Aug. 17, 1875; June 7, 1876; June 17, 1876; Oct. 21, 1876
Victor, Frances Fuller, 1826-1902.
Aug. 1, 1851; Sept. 19, 1852; and Dec. 25, 1852
Victor, Metta Victoria Fuller, 1831-1885.
May 2, 1853; June 26, 1853; Aug. 23, 1853; and Mar. 29, 1854
Weed, Caroline
July 6, 1846; Dec. 9, 1848; Aug. 5, 1851; Mar. 16, 1852; Sept. 22, 1852
Lyman Norris Correspondence
Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.
Sept. 3, 1883
Dickinson, Donald McDonald, 1846-1917.
Nov. 12, 1885; and Nov. 18, 1885
Ferris, Woodbridge N., 1853-1928.
July 3, 1889
Palmer, Thomas Witherell, 1830-1913.
Apr. 27, 1885
Taft, Jonathan, 1820-1903.
July 5, 1883
Woodbridge, William, 1780-1861.
Jan. 20, 1848
Abbott L. Norris Correspondence
Brown, Prentiss Marsh, 1889-1973.
Apr. 20, 1938; Apr. 27, 1938; and Apr. 29, 1938
Ferguson, Homer, 1889-1982.
Jan. 29, 1945; Feb. 6, 1945; Feb. 20, 1945; and July 8, 1946
Jonkman, Bartel J. (Bartel John), 1884-1955-
June 16, 1941; June 18, 1941; July 24, 1941; July 26, 1941; July 28, 1942; Aug. 10, 1942; May 28, 1943; June 1, 1943; June 24, 1943; June 25, 1943; Apr. 28, 1944; May 17, 1944; Aug. 18, 1944; Jan. 29, 1945; Feb. 2, 1945; Feb. 6, 1945; Feb. 13, 1945; Sept. 21, 1945; Feb. 14, 1946; July 8, 1946
Mapes, Carl Edgar, 1874-1939.
Mar. 5, 1935; May 23, 1935; Jan. 16, 1936; Jan. 30, 1937; June 5, 1937; Aug. 20, 1937; Nov. 27, 1937; Jan. 6, 1938; Mar. 1, 1938; Apr. 29, 1938; Dec. 31, 1938; and Jan. 23, 1939; Jan. 7, 1936; Jan. 27, 1937; May 29, 1937; Nov. 18, 1937; Jan. 3, 1938; Feb. 25, 1938; Apr. 27, 1938; Dec. 15, 1938; Jan. 18, 1939; July 11, 1939
Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.
Mar. 4, 1935; May 21, 1935; Jan. 10, 1936; Jan. 30, 1937; June 3, 1937; Nov. 18, 1937; Nov. 23, 1937; Jan. 3, 1938; Jan. 6, 1938; Feb. 25, 1938; Feb. 28, 1938; Apr. 27, 1938; Apr. 29, 1938; Dec. 16, 1938; Dec. 19, 1938; July 11, 1939; Jan. 13, 1940; Jan. 15, 1940; Apr. 25, 1940; Apr. 29, 1940; June 17, 1941; July 24, 1941; July 29, 1941; Feb. 16, 1942; Feb. 19, 1942; Mar. 30, 1942; Apr. 1, 1942; May 12, 1942; May 15, 1942; July 28, 1942; July 31, 1942; May 28, 1943; June 1, 1943; Dec. 3, 1943; Apr. 28, 1944; May 17, 1944; Aug. 18, 1944; Jan. 29, 1945; Feb. 5, 1945; Feb. 6, 1945; June 18, 1945; Sept. 21, 1945; and July 8, 1946
Wheeler, Burton K. (Burton Kendall), 1882-1975.
Jan. 10, 1938; and Jan. 15, 1938